{
    "Items": [
        {
            "question": "Jessica 1._________ (be) a very nice girl.",
            "chinese": "是",
			"correctAns": "is",
			"wrongAns": ["am", "are","aren't"]
        },
		{
			"question": "She always 2._________ (help) other people.",
			"chinese": "幫助",
			"correctAns": "helps",
			"wrongAns": ["helped", "helping", "help"]
		},
		{
			"question": "At home, she often 3._________ (wash) the dishes for her mum?",
			"chinese": "洗",
			"correctAns": "washes",
			"wrongAns": ["wash", "washed", "washing"]
		},
		{
			"question": "and 4._________ (teach) her younger brother to dohishomework.",
			"chinese": "教導",
			"correctAns": "teaches",
			"wrongAns": ["teach", "taught", "teaching" ]
		},
		{
			"question": "Yesterday, when Jessica 5._________ (cross) the road.",
			"chinese": "橫過",
			"correctAns": "crossed",
			"wrongAns": ["cross", "crossing", "crosses"]
		},
		{
			"question": "The old woman 6._________ (walk) very slowly across the road.",
			"chinese": "行",
			"correctAns": "walks",
			"wrongAns": ["walk", "walking", "was walking"]
		},
		{
			"question": "7. (tidy up / room) _________________________",
			"chinese": "XX",
			"correctAns": "I can tidy up my (the) room.",
			"wrongAns": ["I can room my tidy", "I cannot tidy up", "The room is tidy up"]
		},
		{
			"question": "8.(feed / dog) ________________________________",
			"chinese": "XX",
			"correctAns": "I can feed the dog",
			"wrongAns": ["The dog feed me", "Dog is feed", "Feed dog me"]
		},
		{
			"question": "9.(sweep / floor) _______________________",
			"chinese": "XX",
			"correctAns": "I can sweep the floor.",
			"wrongAns": ["The floor sweep me", "The floor is sweep", "Can sweep the floor"]
		},
		{
			"question": "10. (clean / windows) _________________",
			"chinese": "XX",
			"correctAns": "I can clean the windows.",
			"wrongAns": ["I'm clean the windows", "Windows is cleaning", "Windows clean me"]
		},
    ]
}